Bhavin Gajjar

op Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India 🗷 gajjarbhavin22@gmail.com 🗖 +91 8530453855 📠 https://www.linkedin.com/in/bhavingajjar/

▲ https://about.me/bhavingajjar

SUMMARY

Experienced Laravel Developer with over 6+ years in the industry. I have worked on various projects which include challenging and complex structures of the projects like employee training and management software, an online coach learning system, clinical appointment booking, clinical trials management, orthopedic equipment management, a car booking system, dynamic websites with backend admin panel, REST APIs, mortgage leads management system, pos software, etc...

My objective is to seek a career, where I can utilize my quantitative and analytical abilities, quick learning, and adaptability, acquired through my experience to add value to my organization and myself in a dynamic environment

SKILLS

Tools & Technologies: PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter, MySQL, jQuery, JavaScript, AJAX, JSON, REST APIs, Git, Jira, PhpMyAdmin, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, Laravel Lumen, Postman API, React.js

Industry Knowledge: Back-End Web Development, Web Development, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Composer, Web Services, Programming, Technical Training, Technical Leadership, MVC, Livewire, API Development, cURL, Progressive Web Applications (PWAs), PhpStorm, Computer Hardware Assembly, Redis

Interpersonal Skills: Team Leadership Languages: English, Hindi, Gujarati

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

albanero April 2022 - Present, Hyderabad, Telangana, India · Remote

 $Skills: Laravel \cdot Back-End\ Web\ Development \cdot Object-Oriented\ Programming\ (OOP) \cdot API\ Development \cdot Laravel\ Lumen$

Senior Software Engineer

Bacancy Technology: Work From Anywhere August 2021 - March 2022, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · Remote

Skills: Laravel · Jira · Technical Leadership · Team Leadership · React.js

Technical Lead

Techplus Software Private Limited April 2019 - July 2021, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · Remote

Technical Lead of PHP Department

Senior Web Developer

Techplus Software Private Limited

April 2019 - April 2020, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · Hybrid

Skills: Laravel · Laravel Mix · Laravel Lumen

Web Developer

Techplus Software Private Limited May 2017 - March 2019, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · On-site

Skills: CodeIgniter

Trainee Web Developer

Techplus Software Private Limited January 2017 - April 2017, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · On-site

Skills: CodeIgniter · jQuery · AJAX · Git

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Computer Application and Information Technology - M.Sc. (CA & IT), Computer Science Gujarat University · Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · April 2017 · 3.70 / 5 (GPA)

Bachelor of Science in Computer Application and Information Technology - B.Sc. (CA & IT), Computer Software Engineering

Gujarat University · Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India · April 2015 · 2.94 / 5 (GPA)

H.S.C., Commerce Stream

Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board • Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India • March 2012 • 72.43%

PROJECTS

ADAMWILKEYCHIROPRACTOR.COM

Techplus Software Private Limited

- · Technologies: Laravel, Bootstrap 4, jQuery, MySQL
- · This project is for dynamic slot booking for this clinic
- · Lead developer in this project and work within the backend

CLAIMIT OBVIOHEALTH

Techplus Software Private Limited

- · Technologies: Laravel, Bootstrap 4, jQuery, MySQL
- This project is for the study of clinical trials
- · It is a vast portal it includes many projects in it and I work on some of them with a remote team as a Laravel back-end developer in the team

GUNIGURU.COM

Techplus Software Private Limited

- · Technologies: Laravel, Bootstrap 4, ¡Query, MySQL, React.js, Android, IOS
- This project is for an online video coach learning app
- · It is a vast portal it includes many projects in it and I work on some of them as Laravel backend developer in the team

OFFICEAUTOMATEDHUB.COM

Techplus Software Private Limited

- · Technologies: Codeigniter, Bootstrap-3, JQuery, MySQL, Laravel, React.js, Android, IOS
- This project is for an employee attendance system with training & messaging applications, Employees use this system for daily tasks management and history
- · I am the lead developer of this project and work with the team
- · Currently, this whole system refactor into Laravel + React and I had leading back-end rest API tasks

MISCELLANEOUS PROJECTS

Techplus Software Private Limited

• The above projects are long terms projects. I also work worked on many short team projects. Like orthopedic equipment management, cars booking, etc...

leadpops

Bacancy Technology: Work From Anywhere

· working in laravel technology API development

albanero.io

albanero

· working in albanero data mesh platform as a back-end developer

CERTIFICATIONS

PHP Tutorial course

Sololearn · 2016

HTML Fundamentals course

Sololearn · 2016

JavaScript Basics course

Sololearn · 2016

INVOLVEMENT

LARAVEL PACKAGES

https://github.com/bhavingajjar

- · LARAVEL API GENERATOR WITH RESOURCES
- $\cdot \ https://github.com/bhavingajjar/laravel-api-generator$
- · LARAVEL-MAKE-EXTENDER
- $\cdot \ https://github.com/limewell/laravel-make-extender$